millionairemindspro.com 2012-05-08

# Millionaire Minds Pro

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Your privacy is very important to us. I want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and rewarding as possible, and I want you to use the Internet's vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence. 

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. We will notify you of changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new policy on this website. Review our Privacy Policy regularly so that you can stay informed of our practices, as they may change in the future. 

By visiting my site or sending us information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to continue operating this website, including the variety of information and services it contains. Similarly, I need you to provide accurate personal information so that you can be contacted and, if you purchase anything, so that I can complete the transaction. You can opt-out and decide not to provide the requested personal information. However, by doing so, you will not receive the information, product, and/or service you are requesting.

The personal information I collect includes your name and e-mail address. Other personal information that you submit is clearly labeled at the time you submit it. I use the information that I collect to provide our services, fulfill any purchase you may have made, send you our newsletter, contact you regarding new promotions, and to improve our site. I don't use this information—directly or indirectly, or in combination with other parties.

When submitting any information on my website you expressly authorize us to use your personal information as explained in this privacy policy, and you consent to receiving commercial email from me, Rui Ludovino. You can expect to receive newsletters, promotions, and other similar offers. Should you wish to discontinue receiving these e-mailings simply unsubscribe using the link in the email you receive.

We automatically collect certain information from visitors to, the site, such as Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and clickstream data. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve it.

If you pay for anything on my site using a credit or debit card, I collect the personal information needed to complete the transaction. This information includes your name, card number, and other necessary information, all of which is clearly labeled on the form you use to submit payment. We use an unaffiliated, credit card processing company to process your payment. I transfer your payment information—and you authorize us to do so—to this company solely for this purpose. The company does not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

Anything you send me, post on my site, or use with my service, such as blog postings or videos, or if others send us anything about your activities or postings, I may collect such information into a file specific to you. I use this information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our customer agreements.

I take measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information by carefully limiting access to the database in which your personal information is stored. I cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, I may disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. I can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as I, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of wrongful conduct. I may also (and you authorize us to) disclose personal information about you to credit agencies, collection agencies, and/or merchant database agencies, as I deem necessary

I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do I knowingly distribute such information. If I become aware that I have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, I will delete such information from our records. If I change our practices in the future, I will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. 

Contact us at the address below if you want me to change or delete any information that we have about you. I will respond to your request to access, update, or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before I am able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity.

This website is owned and operated, or operated under agreement, by:  
Rui João Marques Ludovino, Rua General Ferreira Martins, Nº1, 1º, Alges, Portugal

This privacy policy is effective as of January 1, 2011.
